Records of the Senior Vice President of Operations
World Bank Group Archives
- Transportation, telecommunication, water, and urban development, 1975 - 1986 (predominantly 1978-1986); WB IBRD/IDA WB_IBRD/IDA_106-01; 9.80 linear feet of textual records
  - Liaison records, 1978 to 1983; WB IBRD/IDA WB_IBRD/IDA_106-01-02; 1.14 linear feet of textual records
    - Transportation, Water and Telecommunications Department - PTWT - World Health Organization [ WHO] - Cooperative Program 1978 - 1980, 1978-01-03 - 1979-02-22; 30048772
    - UNDP/INT/78/013 - Development of the Domestic Construction Industries in Developing Countries - Correspondence, 1978-09-25 - 1978-12-19; 01180274
    - UNDP/INT/77/021 - INT/77/021/A/01/42 - Study of Construction Standards and Methods Appropriate for Simple Building Accomodation Requirements - 1978 / 1980 Documents, 1979-01-01 - 1980-10-31; 30197086
    - UNDP/INT/77/021 - INT/77/021/A/01/42 - Study of Construction Standards and Methods Appropriate for Simple Building Accomodation Requirements - 1978 / 1980 Correspondence, 1978-01-24 - 1979-09-26; 30197085